Shadow of Wars end game is to find
powerful orcs so they can protect your houses.
Yup, it's a fourty hour job except they expect YOU to pay.
So I was very happy when I saw
a level 61 legendary in the arena.
Sadly, you have to sacrifice one of your own to get him in the game.
I didn't want to get rid of anyone with a high level,
But, by happy chance, I had one level 10 orc.
Named Vlad
like the impaler.
Didn't expect a level 61 to take a lot of damage,
But what I really didn't expect
was for him to be KILLED IN ONE HIT
At first I thought it had to be a fluke,
Yet every orc Vlad faced, he killed them in one hit.
So I made him my bodyguard,
and he could do anything, flawlessly.
Kill my opponents...
Slay monsters...
He even defended one of my properties.
Alone.
After that, I no longer considered him my servant.
I considered him my brother.
YEAH HE BETRAYED ME
Which sucks because now I have to kill family.
I took two orcs with me to go crush him.
Which might seem a bit unfair...and it was.
FOR US.
Vlad made the Witch King look like a Chihuahua.
And thats when I decided to forgive him!
...because I knew killing him would take too much time.
Instead I'll go back to focusing on taking down Sauron.
Except, I couldn't.
Vlad had already defeated him.
While I was dead, he had taken over the role as protagonist.
Ruining my game.
That day I decided the one thing I want to do in life
is to kill the traitor!
I took control of every orc on the map
and sent them to erase him.
It went...
Less than stellar...
He literally chopped off the head of every single one of them.
So my army couldnt help me...
The internet couldn't help me...
I didn't even get help.
...from my own government.
There was only one thing, that had always been there for me.
They're called lootboxes.
Lootboxes are a fun way to enhance the gaming experience!
and because you win every time,
It's not gambling.
IT'S NOT GAMBLING.
Through a box I got the Balla Balla Do Do Ona Hitta Bowa
With it I killed Vlad.
Lootboxes saved my game.
And I think thats proof that we should have lootboxes in every single player game.
And if you don't buy them, don't worry about us.
We target people with gambling problems.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S
no gambling
Ha ha! A golden retriever.
Lootboxes: If you don't like them, well, then I guess you're a supporter of Vlad.
Or maybe I should say his full name...
VLADIMIR LENIN
HATING ON MY BOXES MAKES YOU A COMMIE
Remember to check out the links in the description!